export const hiraganas = [
    { problem: 'あ', answer: 'a' },
    { problem: 'い', answer: 'i' },
    { problem: 'う', answer: 'u' },
    { problem: 'え', answer: 'e' },
    { problem: 'お', answer: 'o' },
    { problem: 'か', answer: 'ka' },
    { problem: 'き', answer: 'ki' },
    { problem: 'く', answer: 'ku' },
    { problem: 'け', answer: 'ke' },
    { problem: 'こ', answer: 'ko' },
    { problem: 'さ', answer: 'sa' },
    { problem: 'し', answer: 'shi' },
    { problem: 'す', answer: 'su' },
    { problem: 'せ', answer: 'se' },
    { problem: 'そ', answer: 'so' },
    { problem: 'た', answer: 'ta' },
    { problem: 'ち', answer: 'chi' },
    { problem: 'つ', answer: 'tsu' },
    { problem: 'て', answer: 'te' },
    { problem: 'と', answer: 'to' },
    { problem: 'な', answer: 'na' },
    { problem: 'に', answer: 'ni' },
    { problem: 'ぬ', answer: 'nu' },
    { problem: 'ね', answer: 'ne' },
    { problem: 'の', answer: 'no' },
    { problem: 'は', answer: 'ha' },
    { problem: 'ひ', answer: 'hi' },
    { problem: 'ふ', answer: 'fu' },
    { problem: 'へ', answer: 'he' },
    { problem: 'ほ', answer: 'ho' },
    { problem: 'ま', answer: 'ma' },
    { problem: 'み', answer: 'mi' },
    { problem: 'む', answer: 'mu' },
    { problem: 'め', answer: 'me' },
    { problem: 'も', answer: 'mo' },
    { problem: 'や', answer: 'ya' },
    { problem: 'ゆ', answer: 'yu' },
    { problem: 'よ', answer: 'yo' },
    { problem: 'ら', answer: 'ra' },
    { problem: 'り', answer: 'ri' },
    { problem: 'る', answer: 'ru' },
    { problem: 'れ', answer: 're' },
    { problem: 'ろ', answer: 'ro' },
    { problem: 'わ', answer: 'wa' },
    { problem: 'を', answer: 'o' },
    { problem: 'ん', answer: 'n' }
];

export const katakanas = [
    { problem: 'ア', answer: 'a' },
    { problem: 'イ', answer: 'i' },
    { problem: 'ウ', answer: 'u' },
    { problem: 'エ', answer: 'e' },
    { problem: 'オ', answer: 'o' },
    { problem: 'カ', answer: 'ka' },
    { problem: 'キ', answer: 'ki' },
    { problem: 'ク', answer: 'ku' },
    { problem: 'ケ', answer: 'ke' },
    { problem: 'コ', answer: 'ko' },
    { problem: 'サ', answer: 'sa' },
    { problem: 'シ', answer: 'shi' },
    { problem: 'ス', answer: 'su' },
    { problem: 'セ', answer: 'se' },
    { problem: 'ソ', answer: 'so' },
    { problem: 'タ', answer: 'ta' },
    { problem: 'チ', answer: 'chi' },
    { problem: 'ツ', answer: 'tsu' },
    { problem: 'テ', answer: 'te' },
    { problem: 'ト', answer: 'to' },
    { problem: 'ナ', answer: 'na' },
    { problem: 'ニ', answer: 'ni' },
    { problem: 'ヌ', answer: 'nu' },
    { problem: 'ネ', answer: 'ne' },
    { problem: 'ノ', answer: 'no' },
    { problem: 'ハ', answer: 'ha' },
    { problem: 'ヒ', answer: 'hi' },
    { problem: 'フ', answer: 'fu' },
    { problem: 'ヘ', answer: 'he' },
    { problem: 'ホ', answer: 'ho' },
    { problem: 'マ', answer: 'ma' },
    { problem: 'ミ', answer: 'mi' },
    { problem: 'ム', answer: 'mu' },
    { problem: 'メ', answer: 'me' },
    { problem: 'モ', answer: 'mo' },
    { problem: 'ヤ', answer: 'ya' },
    { problem: 'ユ', answer: 'yu' },
    { problem: 'ヨ', answer: 'yo' },
    { problem: 'ラ', answer: 'ra' },
    { problem: 'リ', answer: 'ri' },
    { problem: 'ル', answer: 'ru' },
    { problem: 'レ', answer: 're' },
    { problem: 'ロ', answer: 'ro' },
    { problem: 'ワ', answer: 'wa' },
    { problem: 'ヲ', answer: 'o' },
    { problem: 'ン', answer: 'n' }
]